Guide to the Adler hip hop archive, circa 1970-2013.
Adler hip hop archive
- Series I. News Files
  - News Files 1980s
    - Performer Names Q-Z
      - Sir Mix-a-Lot, 1989-1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Sleeping Bag Records/Will Socolov, 1989, 2000, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Slick Rick
        - Slick Rick photos, c. 1988-2005 (Box 15, Folder 3)
        - Slick Rick '88-'89, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 4)
        - Slick Rick '90, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
        - Slick Rick '91, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 6)
        - Slick Rick '93, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
        - Slick Rick '94, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 8)
        - Slick Rick '95, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 9)
        - Slick Rick, legal '95, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 10)
        - Slick Rick, correspondence, press releases, etc. '95, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
        - Slick Rick '98-'99, (1996) 1989-1999 (Box 15, Folder 12)
        - Slick Rick '02, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 13)
        - Slick Rick Letters regarding INS problems, June, 2002, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 14)
        - Slick Rick '03, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 15)
        - Slick Rick '04, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 16)
        - Slick Rick '05, 2005-2006 (Box 15, Folder 17)
        - Slick Rick 40th b-day party January 2005, 2005; CD-2147 (Box 15, Folder 17)
        - Slick Rick '06, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 18)
        - Slick Rick - immigration problems, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 19)
        - Slick Rick '07, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 20)
        - Slick Rick '08, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 21)
        - Slick Rick '10-'13, 2010-2013 (Box 15, Folder 22)
        - Slick Rick book-unused lyrics, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 23)
        - Slick Rick book - business, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 24)
        - Slick Rick book-cover art, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 25)
        - Slick Rick book-lyrics, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 26)
        - Slick Rick book-printers, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 27)
        - Slick Rick posters, No Date; FD-11 (Box 15)
      - Michael Small, No Date (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Heidi Smith, c. 1985-2009 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - Larry Smith, c. 1985-2010 (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Larry Smith w/Russell Simmons 1986, No Date; CD-2105 (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Snap, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - The Source (magazine)
        - The source, c. 1990-2006 (Box 15, Folder 32)
        - The Source, c. 1992-2008 (Box 15, Folder 33)
        - Reggie Dennis' account of his time at The Source, c. 1994-2005 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - James Spady, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 35)
        Single letter
      - Special Ed, 1989-1995, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 36)
      - Francesca "Fran" Spero, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 37)
      - Jimmy Spicer, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 38)
      - Spoonie Gee, c. 1983-2007 (Box 15, Folder 39)
      - Spyder D/Sparky D
        - Spyder D/Sparky D '80s, c. 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 40)
        - Spyder D/Sparky D '00-'10, c. 2006-2010 (Box 15, Folder 41)
      - Steady B, 1991-1996, 2002-2006 (Box 15, Folder 42)
      - Bill Stephney, 1992-2012 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Stetsasonic
        - Stetsasonic '86-'88, 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 2)
        - Stetsasonic, "A.F.R.I.C.A." anti-apartheid record, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 3)
        - Stetsasonic '89 and beyond, 1989-1990, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Charlie Stettler, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - "Stop the Violence" Movement, 1988-1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - "Style Wars" (movie), plus Henry Chalfant and Tony Silver, 1984, 2001-2013 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Sugar Hill Records/Sugar Hill Gang/Sylvia Robinson
        - Sugar Hill Gang, Sugar Hill Records, Sylvia Robinson, c. 1979-2006, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 8)
        - Sugar Hill Gang interview for "And You Don't Stop", 2001 (Box 16, Folder 9)
        - Sylvia Robinson interview '05, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 10)
        - Sylvia Robinson obits, '11, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - "Sun City" (all-star anti-apartheid recording), 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Super Lover Cee and Casanova Rud, 1989-1993 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Sweet Gee, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Sweet Tee, 1988-1990 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Greg Tate, 1992-2010 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - 3rd Bass
        - 3rd Bass lyrics, c. 1989 (Box 16, Folder 17)
        - 3rd Bass photos, c. 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 18)
        - 3rd Bass photos, etc, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 19)
        - 3rd Bass - 1990, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 20)
        - 3rd Bass '89, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 21)
        - 3rd Bass '91-'92, 1991-1992, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 22)
        - 3rd Bass U.K. press, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - T. LaRock
        - T. LaRock, 1986-2010 (Box 16, Folder 24)
        - T. LaRock "It's Yours" royalties, 1995-200, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - Jack Thompson, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Three Times Dope, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Tommy Boy Records, 1983-2001 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Too Short
        - Too Short, 1990-2006, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 29)
        - Too Short - Jive Records promo shot, No Date; CD-2094 (Box 16, Folder 29)
        - Too Short in Ozone magazine, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 30)
        - Too Short dust-up in XXL magazine, February 2012, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - Treacherous 3, 1985-2002 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - A Tribe Called Quest
        - A Tribe Called Quest jive, 1990-2005 (Box 16, Folder 33)
        - A Tribe Called Quest movie - "Beats, Rhymes, + Life", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 34)
      - C. Dolores Tucker, 1987-1997, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      - Leyla Turkkan, 1990-1992, 2002-2005 (Box 16, Folder 36)
      - 2 Live Crew/Luke Skyywalker/Luther Campbell
        - 2 Live Crew '90, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 37)
        - 2 Live Crew '91, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 38)
        - Luke '92, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 39)
        - Luke '93, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 40)
        - Luke '94, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 41)
        - 2 Live Crew/Luke bio '95, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 42)
        - Luke '95, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 43)
        - Luke '96-99, 1996-1999 (Box 16, Folder 44)
        - Luke/2 Live Crew '00-'09, 2000-2009 (Box 16, Folder 45)
        - Luke, "Freakfest 2000", 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 46)
        - Luke '10-'13, 2010-2013 (Box 16, Folder 47)
        - Luke '11 (mayoral run), 2011 (Box 16, Folder 48)
      - TVT Records, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 49)
      - Mike Tyson, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 50)
      - Ultramagnetic MCs, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 51)
      - UTFO/"Roxanne, Roxanne" etc, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 52)
        Includes copy of lawsuit against Select Records
      - Van Silk, 1998-2003 (Box 16, Folder 53)
        Copies of Van Silk flyers from the 1980s
      - Akili Walker, No Date (Box 16, Folder 54)
        Includes "Something about the Music" by Akili Walker and Elizabeth Felton. Discography from 1978-2005
      - Wanda Dee, 2004-2006 (Box 16, Folder 55)
      - "The Warriors" (movie), 2005 (Box 16, Folder 56)
        25th Anniversary of the film
      - Wayne and Charlie, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 57)
      - Veronica Webb, 1991-1996 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Whistle, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Whodini
        - Whodini - photos, c. 1982-1987, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 3)
        - Whodini, A. Harrell, scanned images for Hip Hop Honors 2007, 2007; CD-2106 (Box 17, Folder 3)
        - Whodini photos by L. Levine, c. 1982-1987, 2007; CD-2107 (Box 17, Folder 3)
        - Whodini - slides, No Date (Box 17, Folder 4)
        - Whodini '82-'85, 1982-1985, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 5)
          Includes slides
        - Whodini '86, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 6)
        - Whodini '87, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - Whodini '88, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 8)
        - Whodini '90-'96, 1990-1996 (Box 17, Folder 9)
        - Whodini '93 (cops assault Ecstacy), 1993 (Box 17, Folder 10)
        - Whodini '00-'13, 2001-2013 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Emil Wilbekin, c. 1990 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - "Wild Style" (movie) plus Charlie and John Ahearn, 1983-2013 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Winley Records, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Lindsey Williams, 1990-2013 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - "Yes Yes Y'all" (book), 1999-2003 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - "Yo! MTV Raps" (TV show), 1989-2006 (Box 17, Folder 17)
        Includes 7 packs of Yo! MTV Raps trading cards
      - Dr. York, 1990-2002 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Young Black Teenagers, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - News Files 1990s and 2000s
    - Performer Names A-H
      - Aaliyah, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Above the Law, c. 1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Ace Hood, 2011-2013 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Aceyalone, 1995-1998 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Aesop Rock, c. 2000-2012 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Afroman, No Date (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Afros, 1990-1991, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Afu-Ra, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Akinyele, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Akon, 2004-2011 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - The Alchemist, No Date (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Chi Ali, 1992-1993, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Ali Dee, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Tha Alkaholiks/Tha Liks, 1993-2006 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Almighty RSO (also Made Men and Ray Benzino), 1992-2002 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - AMG, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Deric "D-Dot" Angelettie, 1999-2002 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Anquette, No Date (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - "Anthology of Rap" (book), 2011 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Apache, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Apache Indian, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Arrested Development
        - Arrested Development '91-'93, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 22)
        - Arrested Development photos, No Date (Box 18, Folder 23)
        - Arrested Development '94-'13, 1993-2013 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Artifacts, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - ASAP Rocky (and associates), 2013 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - Ashanti, 2002-2004 (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - AZ, 1995, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - "Backstage" (documentary film), c. 2000 (Box 18, Folder 29)
      - Erykah Badu, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 30)
      - Bahamadia, 1994-1995, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 31)
      - Charli Baltimore, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 32)
      - Ant Banks, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 33)
      - Azealia Banks, 2012-2013 (Box 18, Folder 34)
      - Lloyd Banks, 2004-2012 (Box 18, Folder 35)
      - David Banner, 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 36)
      - Buju Banton, 1993-2012 (Box 18, Folder 37)
      - Da Beatminerz, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 38)
      - The Beatnuts
        - The Beatnuts - photos, 1994, No Date (Box 18, Folder 39)
        - The Beatnuts, 1992-2002 (Box 18, Folder 40)
      - Beenie Man, 2000-2005 (Box 18, Folder 41)
      - James Bernard, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 42)
        Manifest magazine
      - B.G., 2000, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 43)
      - Big Boi, 2004-2011 (Box 18, Folder 44)
      - Big Freedia, 2010-2013 (Box 18, Folder 45)
      - Biggie Smalls a/k/a the Notorious B.I.G.
        - Notorious B.I.G. - Bad Boy/Arista, 1992-2011 (Box 18, Folder 46)
        - Notorious B.I.G. - Born Again, 1994-1995, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 47)
        - Biggie Smalls death, 1999-2013 (Box 18, Folder 48)
      - Big K.R.I.T., 2012 (Box 18, Folder 49)
      - Big L, 1995-2011 (Box 18, Folder 50)
      - Big Mike, 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 51)
      - Big Moe, 2002-2013 (Box 18, Folder 52)
      - Big Noyd, No Date (Box 18, Folder 53)
      - Big Pun a/k/a Big Punisher
        - Big Pun - bios, photos, p.r., ads, 1998-2001, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 54)
        - Big Pun - press, 1998-2001 (Box 18, Folder 55)
      - Big Shug, No Date (Box 18, Folder 56)
      - Big Tigger Celebrity Birthday Bash, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 57)
      - Big Tymers, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 58)
      - Blackalicious, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 59)
      - "Black and White" (movie), 2000 (Box 18, Folder 60)
      - Black Eyed Peas, 1997-2011 (Box 18, Folder 61)
      - Black Moon, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 62)
      - Black Rob, 1999-2000, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 63)
      - Black Sheep, 1991-2006 (Box 18, Folder 64)
      - Black Star, 1998-2000 (Box 18, Folder 65)
      - Blahzay-Blahzay, c. 1995-1999 (Box 18, Folder 66)
      - Mary J. Blige, 1995-2004 (Box 18, Folder 67)
      - Blood of Abraham, 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 68)
      - B.O.B., 2010 (Box 18, Folder 69)
      - Bone Crusher, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 70)
      - Bone Thugs-n-Harmony
        - Bone Thugs-n-Harmony - press, 1997-2007 (Box 18, Folder 71)
        - Bone Thugs-n-Harmony: bios, press releases, etc., 1994-2002 (Box 18, Folder 72)
      - Boo-Yaa T.R.I.B.E., 1990-2000 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Boss, 1992-1993, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Bounty Killer, No Date (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - "Boyz n the Hood" (movie), 1991,2000 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Charlie Braxton, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Foxy Brown
        - Foxy Brown, 1997-2008 (Box 19, Folder 6)
        - Foxy Brown, 1997-2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Joe Budden, 2007-2009 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - "Bulworth" (movie), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Bushwackas, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Bushwick Bill, 1991-2002 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Busta Rhymes
        - Busta Rhymes, 1999-2011 (Box 19, Folder 12)
        - Busta Rhymes, 1996-2011 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Rev. Calvin Butts, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Bytches With Problems a/k/a BWP, 1990-1991, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Cam'Ron, 1999-2013 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Camp Lo, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Canibus, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Capleton, 1994-1996 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Capone-n-Noreaga, 2000-2006, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Cappadonna, No Date (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Case, 1996-2004 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Cash Money Records, 1998-2012 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Casual, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - "CB4" (movie), 1993 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - C-BO, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Cee-Lo, 2002-2011 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Cella Dwellas, No Date (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Raquel Cepeda, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Chamillionaire, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Jeff Chang
        - Jeff Chang, 2001-2010 (Box 19, Folder 31)
        - Cant Stop Won't Stop - first draft 11/01/03, 2003; CD-2110 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - Channel Live, 1994-2000 (Box 19, Folder 32)
      - "Chicken Noodle Soup" (song by Webstar and Young B), 2006 (Box 19, Folder 33)
      - Farai Chideya, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 34)
      - Chingo Bling, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 35)
      - Chingy, 2003-2007 (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - Chino XL, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 37)
      - Mary Choi, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 38)
      - Choppa, No Date (Box 19, Folder 39)
      - The Chop Up (TV show)
        - "The Chop Up", 2006 (Box 19, Folder 40)
        - The Chop Up - Show 102, 2006; DVD-1075 (Box 19, Folder 40)
      - Cipha Sounds, c. 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 41)
      - Clipse, 2003-2008 (Box 19, Folder 42)
      - C-Murder, 2002-2011 (Box 19, Folder 43)
      - Cocoa Brovaz, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 44)
      - Coco Tea, No Date (Box 19, Folder 45)
      - Cheo H. Coker, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 46)
      - Keyshia Cole, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 47)
      - Brian Coleman, No Date (Box 19, Folder 48)
      - Sean Combs, a/k/a Puff Daddy, Puffy, and P. Diddy
        - Puff Daddy '90s, 1990s (Box 19, Folder 49)
        - Puff Daddy/Heavy D Stampede at CCNY, 1991-1999 (Box 19, Folder 50)
        - Puffy '00, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 51)
        - Puffy newspapers, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 52)
        - Puffy mags, print-outs, ads etc, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 53)
        - Puffy '02, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 54)
        - Puffy '03, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 55)
        - Puffy '04, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 56)
        - Puffy '05, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 57)
        - Puffy '06-'11, 2006-2011 (Box 19, Folder 58)
        - Puffy advertising, 2006-2011 (Box 19, Folder 59)
      - Common a/k/a Common Sense, 1994-2013 (Box 19, Folder 60)
      - Company Flow, 1997-2007 (Box 19, Folder 61)
      - Conscious Daughters, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 62)
      - Coolio, 1993-2013 (Box 19, Folder 63)
      - Barry Michael Cooper, 1994, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 64)
      - Core, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 65)
      - Cormega, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 66)
      - The Coup, 1992-1998 (Box 19, Folder 67)
      - Craig G., 1991 (Box 19, Folder 68)
      - Crime Mob, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 69)
      - Crucial Conflict, No Date (Box 19, Folder 70)
      - Crustified Dibbs, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 71)
      - Cuban Link, 2001-2005 (Box 19, Folder 72)
      - Cypress Hill, 1991-2006 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Da Brat, 1995-2007 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Da Bush Babees, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Da Lench Mob, 1992-1994 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Da Youngsta's, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Daddy Freddy, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Daddy Yankee, 2006-2008 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Danger Mouse, 2006-2012 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Dangerous D, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Das EFX, 1992-1995, 2001-2006 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Damon Dash, 2002-2010 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Davey D. (Bay Area journalist Dave Cook), 2001-2003 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Wendy Day/Rap Coalition, 1992-1995, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Dead Prez, 1999-2006 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Def Squad (on Def Jam), 1992-1998, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Def Squad (on Mr. Henry), 1994 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Defari, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Del the Funky Homosapien/Del Tha Funkee Homosapien, 1992-1994 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Dem Franchize Boyz, 2006-2008 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Ted Demme, 2001-2002, 2012 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Devin the Dude, 2004-2008 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Diamond D, 2002-2010 (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Digable Planets, 1992-1995, 2002-2007 (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - Dilated Peoples, 1998-2004 (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Daz Dillinger, c. 1998 (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - Diplomats, 2005, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 26)
      - Disco D, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 27)
      - D.I.T.C, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - Dizzee Rascal, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 29)
      - DJ Assault, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 30)
      - DJ Camilo, 2006-2013 (Box 20, Folder 31)
      - DJ Clue, 1998-2012 (Box 20, Folder 32)
      - DJ Drama, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 33)
      - DJ EFN, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 34)
      - DJ Enuff, 2004-2013 (Box 20, Folder 35)
      - DJ Envy, 2006-2013 (Box 20, Folder 36)
      - DJ Faze, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 37)
      - DJ Hurricane, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 38)
      - DJ Hurricane manuscript of a memoir, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 39)
      - DJ Kay, 2011-2012 (Box 20, Folder 40)
      - DJ Khaled, 2007-2013 (Box 20, Folder 41)
      - D.J. Magic Mike, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 42)
      - DJ Pooh, 1993-1994, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 43)
      - DJ Quik, 1991-2011 (Box 20, Folder 44)
      - DJ Premier, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 45)
      - DJ Scratch, No Date (Box 20, Folder 46)
      - DJ Screw, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 47)
      - DJ Self, 2010-2013 (Box 20, Folder 48)
      - DJ Shadow, 2012 (Box 20, Folder 49)
      - DJ Skribble, c. 2004 (Box 20, Folder 50)
      - DJ Spooky, 1994-1998, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 51)
      - DJ Suss One, c. 2011 (Box 20, Folder 52)
      - DMX
        - DMX - photos, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 53)
        - DMX - bios, ads, business correspondence, etc., 1997-2004, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 54)
        - Business correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 45, Folder 14)
          RESTRICTED until 2050 - Moved from Box 20, Folder 54 to Box 45, Folder 14
        - DMX - VH1 Behind the Music, 2010; DVD-1076 (Box 20, Folder 54)
        - DMX - press copies, 1998-2001 (Box 20, Folder 55)
        - DMX - newspapers, 1998-2012 (Box 20, Folder 56)
        - DMX - magazines, 1998-2011 (Box 20, Folder 57)
        - DMX - articles, No Date; CD-2111 (Box 20, Folder 57)
      - Tony Dofat, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 58)
      - Domino, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 59)
      - Tha Dogg Pound, 1995, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 60)
      - Dove Shack, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 61)
      - Downtown Science, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 62)
      - Drag-On, 1999-2003 (Box 20, Folder 63)
      - Drake, 2009-2012 (Box 20, Folder 64)
      - Dr. Dre
        - Dr. Dre "Chronic Tour" '93, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 65)
        - Dr. Dre bios, photos, ads, etc., 1992-2004 (Box 20, Folder 66)
        - Dr. Dre '90-'99, 1990-1999 (Box 20, Folder 67)
        - Dr. Dre '00-'13, 2000-2013 (Box 20, Folder 68)
      - Dr. Octagon, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 69)
      - Dre, No Date (Box 20, Folder 70)
      - Drag-on, 2010-2012 (Box 20, Folder 71)
      - Dru Down, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 72)
      - Jermaine Dupri, 1995-2007 (Box 20, Folder 73)
      - Michael Eric Dyson, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 74)
      - The Eastsidaz, c. 2001 (Box 20, Folder 75)
      - Eazy E
        - Eazy-E, 1990-2006 (Box 20, Folder 76)
        - Eazy-E - "The Impact of a Legend", No Date; CD-2112-2113 (Box 20, Folder 76)
        - Eazy-E dies, 3/95, 1995-2002, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 77)
      - Easy Mo Bee, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 78)
      - Ed O.G. and Da Bulldogs, 1991-1994, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 79)
      - E-40, 1994-2013 (Box 20, Folder 80)
      - ego trip (magazine, books, TV shows)
        - Ego trip '04, 2004-2009 (Box 21, Folder 1)
        - "Ego trip's Big Book of Racism", 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 2)
        - "Ego trip's Book of Rap Lists", 1998-2002 (Box 21, Folder 3)
        - Ego trip, 1996-2007 (Box 21, Folder 4)
        - Ego trip - photos by Bill Adler '99, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - 8ball and MJG, 1995-2012 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Elephant Man, 2002-2008 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Missy Elliot, 1997-2008 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Eminem
        - Eminem photos and bios, 1999-2004 (Box 21, Folder 9)
        - Eminem '98-'99, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 10)
        - Eminem '00, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 11)
        - Eminem '01, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 12)
        - Eminem '02, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 13)
        - Eminem '03, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 14)
        - Eminem '04-'05, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 15)
        - Eminem (and D12) '06, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 16)
        - Eminem '07-'13, 2007-2013 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - E.S.G., No Date (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Kodwo Eshun author of "More Brilliant than the Sun" (book), 1998 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Essence Donn, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Eve, 1999-2011 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Eve Scans 3/29/10, 2010; CD-2142 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Everlast, 1998-2001 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Extra Prolific, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - Fabolous, 2001-2010 (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - Fat Joe, 1993-2005, 2012 (Box 21, Folder 25)
      - Father MC, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 26)
      - "Fear of a Black Hat" (movie), 1994, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 27)
      - Lupe Fiasco, 2007-2012 (Box 21, Folder 28)
      - Field Mob, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 29)
      - 5th Ward Boyz, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 30)
      - 504 Boyz, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 31)
      - 50 Cent
        - 50 Cent bios, photos, ads, etc, c. 2002-2005 (Box 21, Folder 32)
        - "Get Rich or Die Trying" (album), No Date; DVD-1077 (Box 21, Folder 32)
        - 50 Cent, 2000-2012 (Box 21, Folder 33)
      - Flatlinerz, 1991-1994 (Box 21, Folder 34)
      - Flavor-Flav, 1991-2013 (Box 21, Folder 35)
      - VH1 Celebreality - including Flavor Flav in "Strange Love", 2005; CD-2143 (Box 21, Folder 35)
      - Flo Rida, 2012 (Box 21, Folder 36)
      - John Forte, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 37)
      - Freddie Foxxx, 1989-2000 (Box 21, Folder 38)
      - Sage Francis Lyrics, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 39)
      - Free, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 40)
      - Freestyle Fellowship, 1992-2011 (Box 21, Folder 41)
      - Freeway, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 42)
      - French Rap miscellaneous, 1990-1996 (Box 21, Folder 43)
        Copies of articles
      - Mannie Fresh, 2005-2007 (Box 21, Folder 44)
      - FUBU, 1994-2001 (Box 21, Folder 45)
      - Fugees, 1993-2010 (Box 21, Folder 46)
      - Fun-da-mental, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 47)
      - Funkdoobiest, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 48)
      - Funkmaster Flex a/k/a Funk Flex